<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Aspergent</title>
    <link href="https://aspergent.tk/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://aspergent.tk" />
    <updated>1969-12-31T19:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Harry</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://aspergent.tk</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Travelling.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Harry</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://aspergent.tk/travelling.html"/>
        <id>https://aspergent.tk/travelling.html</id>

        <updated>2020-08-06T20:41:09-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <hr class="separator separator--long-line" />

  <p>
    Everyone has something they hate. Their daily 9-5's, their depressing conditions of which they live in, even, just the state they're currently in. I personally follow the hatred of living in one state. I inherited my mom's nomadic spirit. She, in her last year of college went to escaped Delaware, and planned to be in Colorado.&nbsp;
  </p>

    <figure class="blockquote">
      <blockquote>Hiking is not escapism; it's realism. The people who choose to spend time outdoors are not running away from anything; we are returning to where we belong.</blockquote>
      <figcaption>Jennifer Pharr Davis, The Pursuit of Endurance: Harnessing the Record-Breaking Power of Strength and Resilience</figcaption>
    </figure>

  <p>
    For the longest time, I've wanted to travel. I became addicted to the thought of having a tiny home. When quarantine hit us, my need for travel became stronger than ever. I have never felt the way about home that I feel now. I just hate it. Other people in my family have a hard time grasping why I hold such hatred for where our roots were placed. Others, are quite supportive of my nomadic heart. It's hard to not make traveling my main obsession. It just is how I am. I don't want my roots placed somewhere where my heart isn't.&nbsp; My heart isn't in Delaware. It never was.
  </p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <hr class="separator separator--long-line" />

  <p>
    Everyone has something they hate. Their daily 9-5's, their depressing conditions of which they live in, even, just the state they're currently in. I personally follow the hatred of living in one state. I inherited my mom's nomadic spirit. She, in her last year of college went to escaped Delaware, and planned to be in Colorado.&nbsp;
  </p>

    <figure class="blockquote">
      <blockquote>Hiking is not escapism; it's realism. The people who choose to spend time outdoors are not running away from anything; we are returning to where we belong.</blockquote>
      <figcaption>Jennifer Pharr Davis, The Pursuit of Endurance: Harnessing the Record-Breaking Power of Strength and Resilience</figcaption>
    </figure>

  <p>
    For the longest time, I've wanted to travel. I became addicted to the thought of having a tiny home. When quarantine hit us, my need for travel became stronger than ever. I have never felt the way about home that I feel now. I just hate it. Other people in my family have a hard time grasping why I hold such hatred for where our roots were placed. Others, are quite supportive of my nomadic heart. It's hard to not make traveling my main obsession. It just is how I am. I don't want my roots placed somewhere where my heart isn't.&nbsp; My heart isn't in Delaware. It never was.
  </p>
<hr id="read-more" />

  <p>
    It's not that I hate the people, or the locale, but it is. Delaware has a form of blandness to it. Monotony at it's finest. We're not known for anything other than being <em>the first state</em>, or where Joe Biden resides. Our state is known for the University of Delaware, and beaches.
  </p>

  <p>
    I had a conversation with my dad while we were at Costco. I was trying to explain to him why I hate Delaware so much. I brought up that we're not known for anything. I asked him to name different states, to prove that we're known for nothing. He brought up New Mexico. To his surprise, I proved that New Mexico was actually known for something. A town in the state produced majority of the Uranium used by the military from WWII to The Cold War. They have the most PHD's per capita. Again, They're known for something good.
  </p>

    <h2 id="the-reason-behind-my-stronger-need-is-just-from-the-internetbrbr">
      The reason behind my stronger need is just from the internet.<br><br>
    </h2>

  <p>
    It feels.. Odd, that at the age of fourteen, I have the mentality of someone much older. The internet quite frankly has always been a coping mechanic, but it's just been nothing more than trouble in the past few months. I see channels like Elsa Rhae and Barron, Kara and Nate, Janelle Eliana, and they just prove that I'm not the only one who feels like this lifestyle is what I want. These are people who make me feel normal. A sense of reality coming to me.
  </p>

    <figure class="blockquote">
      <blockquote>I don’t think the homesickness of a perpetual wanderer can ever be quenched.</blockquote>
      <figcaption>Sasha Martin, Life from Scratch: A Memoir of Food, Family, and Forgiveness</figcaption>
    </figure>

  <p>
    I feel homesick most days. It's quite weird since I am home, but my spirit isn't. I'm mentally never home, always wandering. I can thank being aspergent for it. The hell that autism creates, is a wandering mind. We just came home from a trip I absolutely despised until I got there. Buxton, North Carolina, is such a beautiful town. The waves and the breeze call me. It signals a better future ahead. Something to keep me sane.
  </p>

  <p>
    <br>
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
